Guide to the Office of the President Records, Alan Simpson Files, 1949-1979
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series III. Faculty, 1955-1978
  - Religion — Officers, 1969-1970 (Folder 31.39)
  - Russian — Officers, 1969-1970 (Folder 31.40)
  - Acting Dean of Faculty — Miss Marion Tait, 1970-1971 (Folder 31.41)
  - Dean of Faculty, 1972-1973 (Folder 31.42)
  - Acting Dean of Faculty — I. Fox, 1971-1972 (Folder 31.43)
  - Barbara Wells — Dean Elect, 1971-1972 (Folder 31.44)
  - Dean of Faculty Reports to Trustees, 1972-1973 (Folder 31.45)
  - Acting Dean of Faculty Reports to Trustees, 1970-1972 (Folder 31.46)
  - House Fellows, 1970-1973 (Folder 31.47)
  - Registrar, 1970-1971 (Folder 31.48)
  - Committee on Deanship, 1970-1971 (Folder 31.49)
  - Candidate for Deanship — Doreen Boyce, 1970 (Folder 31.50)
  - Candidate for Deanship — Marilyn Gittell, 1970 (Folder 31.51)
  - Candidate for Deanship — Joyce Godol, 1971 (Folder 31.52)
  - Candidate for Deanship — Angeliki Laiou, 1970 (Folder 31.53)
  - Candidate for Deanship — Sally Sperling, 1970-1971 (Folder 31.54)
  - Candidate for Deanship — Ann Wirt, 1970-1971 (Folder 31.55)
  - Office of Dean of Studies, 1972-1973 (Folder 31.56)
  - Dean of Studies, 1970-1972 (Folder 31.57)
  - Dean of Freshmen, 1971-1972 (Folder 31.58)
  - Dean of Freshmen, 1972-1973 (Folder 31.59)
  - Vice President of Student Affairs, 1970-1973 (Folder 31.60)
  - Director of Financial Aid, 1970-1973 (Folder 31.61)
  - Vocational Bureau, 1971 (Folder 31.62)
  - Career Planning, 1972-1973 (Folder 31.63)
  - Director of Student Activities, 1973 (Folder 31.64)
  - Chaplain, 1971-1973 (Folder 31.65)
  - Dean of Residence, 1971-1973 (Folder 31.66)
  - Director of Admissions (Mr. Stephenson), 1970-1973 (Folder 31.67)
  - Committee on Admission, 1970-1973 (Folder 31.68)
  - Audubon Elephant Folio, 1972-1973 (Folder 31.69)
  - Library — Rare Book Room Children’s Books, 1963-1973 (Folder 31.70)
  - Art Library — Conversion of Art Reading Room, 1971 (Folder 31.71)
  - Library — Proposed Expansion, 1970-1971 (Folder 31.72)
  - Library — Officers, 1970-1973 (Folder 31.73)
  - Sociology — Committee to Review long-range Plans, 1971 (Folder 32.1)
  - Recruitment — Anthropology, 1967-1968 (Folder 32.2)
  - Sociology-Anthropology — Applicants, 1968-1970 (Folder 32.3)
  - Economics, Sociology, Anthropology — Applicants, 1966-1968 (Folder 32.4)
  - Anthropology-Sociology — Applicants, 1970-1973 (Folder 32.5)
  - Anthropology-Sociology — Officers, 1970-1973 (Folder 32.6)
  - Art — Applicants, 1970-1972 (Folder 32.7)
  - Committee on Outdoor Exhibitions of Sculpture, 1972 (Folder 32.8)
  - Art Gallery, 1970-1973 (Folder 32.9)
  - Art — Officers, 1970-1973 (Folder 32.10)
  - Biology — Applicants, 1971-1972 (Folder 32.11)
  - Biology Department — Cary Estate and New York Botanical Garden, 1972 (Folder 32.12)
  - Biology — Officers, 1971-1973 (Folder 32.13)
  - Chemistry — Applicants, 1971-1972 (Folder 32.14)
  - Chemistry — Officers, 1970-1973 (Folder 32.15)
  - Classics — Applicants, 1972 (Folder 32.16)
  - Classics — Officers, 1971-1973 (Folder 32.17)
  - Drama — Applicants, 1970-1973 (Folder 32.18)
  - Drama — Officers, 1970-1973 (Folder 32.19)
  - Economics — Applicants, 1970-1973 (Folder 32.20)
  - Economics — Officers, 1970-1973 (Folder 32.21)
  - Education — Applicants, 1972-1973 (Folder 32.22)
  - Education — Officers, 1970-1972 (Folder 32.23)
  - English — Applicants, 1970-1973 (Folder 32.24)
  - English — Officers, 1970-1973 (Folder 32.25)
  - French — Applicants, 1972-1973 (Folder 32.26)
  - French — Officers, 1970-1973 (Folder 32.27)
  - Geology-Geography — Applicants, 1972 (Folder 32.28)
  - Geology-Geography — Officers, 1970-1973 (Folder 32.29)
  - German — Applicants, 1972 (Folder 32.30)
  - German — Officers, 1970-1973 (Folder 32.31)
  - Health — Officers, 1971-1972 (Folder 32.32)
  - Health — Psychiatrist, 1971-1973 (Folder 32.33)
  - Hispanic Studies — Applicants, 1973 (Folder 32.34)
  - Hispanic Studies, 1970-1973 (Folder 32.35)
  - History — Applicants, 1970-1973 (Folder 32.36)
  - Oral History of Vassar College, 1972 (Folder 32.37)
  - History — Officers, 1970-1973 (Folder 32.38)
  - Italian — Officers, 1970-1973 (Folder 32.39)
  - Mathematics — Applicants, 1972-1973 (Folder 32.40)
  - Mathematics — Officers, 1971-1973 (Folder 32.41)
  - Music — Applicants, 1972-1973 (Folder 32.42)
  - Music Officers, 1970-1973 (Folder 32.43)
  - Philosophy — Applicants, 1970-1973 (Folder 32.44)
  - Philosophy — Officers, 1970-1973 (Folder 32.45)
  - Physical Education — Applicants, 1972 (Folder 32.46)
  - Physical Education — Officers, 1970-1973 (Folder 32.47)
  - Physics-Astronomy — Applicants, 1971-1972 (Folder 32.48)
  - Physics-Astronomy — Officers, 1970-1973 (Folder 32.49)
  - Political Science — Applicants, 1971-1973 (Folder 32.50)
  - Political Science — Officers, 1970-1973 (Folder 32.51)
  - Psychology — Applicants, 1972-1973 (Folder 32.52)
  - Psychology — Officers, 1970-1973 (Folder 32.53)
  - Religion — Applicants, 1970-1973 (Folder 32.54)
  - Religion — Officers, 1970-1973 (Folder 32.55)
  - Russian — Applicants, 1973 (Folder 32.56)
  - Russian — Officers, 1971-1973 (Folder 32.57)
  - Anthropology-Sociology — Applicants, 1974-1975 (Folder 32.58)
  - Anthropology-Sociology — Officers, 1973-1975 (Folder 32.59)
  - Art — Applicants, 1973-1975 (Folder 32.60)
  - Art Gallery, 1973-1976 (Folder 32.61)
  - Art Gallery, 1974-1977 (Folder 32.62)
  - Art Gallery, 1976-1978 (Folder 32.63)
  - Art — Officers, 1973-1976 (Folder 32.64)
  - Friends of the Art Gallery, 1975-1976 (Folder 32.65)
  - Friends of the art Gallery, 1973-1975 (Folder 32.66)
  - Art, 1976-1978 (Folder 32.67)
  - Biology — Applicants, 1974-1976 (Folder 32.68)
  - Biology — Officers, 1973-1976 (Folder 32.69)
  - Biology Departments, 1976-1978 (Folder 32.70)
  - Biology Building Dedication, 1973-1974 (Folder 32.71)
  - Chemistry — Applicants, 1973-1974 (Folder 32.72)
  - Chemistry — Officers, 1974-1976 (Folder 32.73)
  - Chemistry, 1977-1978 (Folder 32.74)
  - Classics — Applicants, 1975 (Folder 32.75)
  - Classics — Officers, 1974-1975 (Folder 32.76)
  - Drama — Applicants, 1974-1975 (Folder 33.1)
  - Drama — Officers, 1973-1976 (Folder 33.2)
  - Drama, 1976-1978 (Folder 33.3)
  - Economics — Applicant, 1974-1976 (Folder 33.4)
  - Economics — Officers, 1974-1976 (Folder 33.5)
  - Economics, 1977-1978 (Folder 33.6)
  - Education — Search Committee for Chairman of Department, 1974 (Folder 33.7)
  - Education — Applicants, 1973-1976 (Folder 33.8)
  - Education — Officers, 1973-1976 (Folder 33.9)
  - English — Applicants, 1973-1976 (Folder 33.10)
  - English Candidate — Richard A. Steuble, 1974 (Folder 33.11)
  - English — Officers, 1973-1975 (Folder 33.12)
  - Sylvia Plath’s Papers — Correspondence in re, 1971-1975 (Folder 33.13)
  - French — Applicants, 1975 (Folder 33.14)
  - French — Officers, 1974-1975 (Folder 33.15)
  - Geology-Geography — Applicants, 1974-1976 (Folder 33.16)
  - Geology-Geography — Officers, 1973-1978 (Folder 33.17)
  - German — Applicants, 1974 (Folder 33.18)
  - German — Officers, 1974-1975 (Folder 33.19)
  - Health — Applicants, 1973-1974; (empty) (Folder 33.20)
  - Director of Counseling Services and Psychiatrist, 1974-1975 (Folder 33.21)
  - Health — Officers, 1975-1976 (Folder 33.22)
  - Hispanic Studies — Applicants, 1974-1976 (Folder 33.23)
  - Hispanic Studies — Officers, 1974-1975 (Folder 33.24)
  - History — Applicants, 1974-1975 (Folder 33.25)
  - History — Officers, 1974-1976 (Folder 33.26)
  - C. Mildred Thompson Symposium, 1975 Nov (Folder 33.27)
  - Italian — Applicants, 1975-1976 (Folder 33.28)
  - Italian — Officers, 1973-1976 (Folder 33.29)
  - Library, 1976-1978 (Folder 33.30)
  - Cornaro Tercentenary Committee, 1973-1976 (Folder 33.31)
  - Helen D. Lockwood Library, 1973-1974 (Folder 33.32)
  - Library Officers, 1973-1976 (Folder 33.33)
  - Mathematics — Applicants, 1973-1975 (Folder 33.34)
  - Mathematics — Officers, 1974-1976 (Folder 33.35)
  - Music — Applicants, 1973-1976 (Folder 33.36)
  - Music — Officers, 1973-1976 (Folder 33.37)
  - Philosophy — Applicants, 1974-1975 (Folder 33.38)
  - Philosophy — Officers, 1973-1975 (Folder 33.39)
  - Physical Education — Applicants, 1974-1976 (Folder 33.40)
  - Physical Education — Officers, 1973-1976 (Folder 33.41)
  - Physical Education, 1976-1978 (Folder 33.42)
  - Physics-Astronomy, 1974-1976 (Folder 33.43)
  - Physics-Astronomy — Officers, 1973-1976 (Folder 33.44)
  - Political Science — Applicants, 1974-1976 (Folder 33.45)
  - Political Science — Officers, 1973-1976 (Folder 33.46)
  - Psychology — Applicants, 1974-1975 (Folder 33.47)
  - Psychology — Officers, 1973-1976 (Folder 33.48)
  - Religion — Applicants, 1973-1976 (Folder 33.49)
  - Religion — Officers, 1973-1976 (Folder 33.50)
  - Russian — Applicants, 1974 (Folder 33.51)
  - Russian — Officers, 1974-1975 (Folder 33.52)
  - Science, Technology and Society (STS), 1976-1978 (Folder 33.53)
- Series IV. Alumnae/i, 1949-1979
  - Alumnae — A, 1963-1967 (Folder 33.54)
  - Alumnae — B, 1963-1967 (Folder 33.55)
  - Alumnae — C, 1963-1967 (Folder 33.56)
  - Alumnae — D, 1963-1967 (Folder 33.57)
  - Alumnae — E, 1963-1965 (Folder 33.58)
  - Alumnae — F, 1963-1966 (Folder 33.59)
  - Alumnae — G, 1963-1967 (Folder 33.60)
  - Alumnae — H, 1963-1967 (Folder 33.61)
  - Alumnae — I, 1963-1964 (Folder 33.62)
  - Alumnae — J, 1964-1966 (Folder 33.63)
  - Alumnae — K, 1963-1967 (Folder 33.64)
  - Alumnae — L, 1962-1967 (Folder 33.65)
  - Alumnae — M, 1963-1967 (Folder 34.1)
  - Mary McCarthy — “The Group”, 1963-1966 (Folder 34.2)
  - Alumnae — N, 1964-1966 (Folder 34.3)
  - Alumnae — O, 1963-1967 (Folder 34.4)
  - Alumnae — P, 1963-1967 (Folder 34.5)
  - Alumnae — Q, 1965-1966 (Folder 34.6)
  - Alumnae — R, 1963-1967 (Folder 34.7)
  - Alumnae — S, 1963-1967 (Folder 34.8)
  - Alumnae — T, 1963-1966 (Folder 34.9)
  - Alumnae — U, (empty) (Folder 34.10)
  - Alumnae — V, 1963-1966 (Folder 34.11)
  - Alumnae — W, 1963-1967 (Folder 34.12)
  - Alumnae — W-Y-Z, 1963-1966 (Folder 34.13)
  - Associate Alumnae, 1963-1964 (Folder 34.14)
  - Associate Alumnae, 1964-1965 (Folder 34.15)
  - Associate Alumnae, 1965-1966 (Folder 34.16)
  - Associate Alumnae, 1966-1967 (Folder 34.17)
  - AAVC Council Meeting, 1967 Apr (Folder 34.18)
  - Alumnae Reunions, 1964-1967 (Folder 34.19)
  - Vassar Opera, 1964-1969 (Folder 34.20)
  - Alumnae Magazine, 1964-1966 (Folder 34.21)
  - Classroom Program, 1965-1967 (Folder 34.22)
  - Poughkeepsie Vassar Club, 1965 (Folder 34.23)
  - Philadelphia Vassar Club, 1965-1966 (Folder 34.24)
  - New York Vassar Club, 1964-1967 (Folder 34.25)
  - Mr. Simpson’s Trips, primarily to visit Vassar Clubs, 1964-1965 (Folder 34.26)
  - Washington-Philadelphia Trip, 1964 Nov (Folder 34.27)
  - Boston Vassar Club, 1965 Mar (Folder 34.28)
  - Detroit and Chicago Trip, 1965 May (Folder 34.29)
  - Hartford Vassar Club, 1965 Sep (Folder 34.30)
  - Woman’s College Board of Chicago, 1964-1965 (Folder 34.31)
  - New Haven Vassar Club, 1965 Oct (Folder 34.32)
  - Minneapolis/St. Paul Trip, 1965 Nov (Folder 34.33)
  - Minnesota, 1968 May (Folder 34.34)
  - St. Louis/Kansas City Trip, 1966 Apr (Folder 34.35)
  - Westchester Vassar Club, 1966 May (Folder 34.36)
  - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, 1966 (Folder 34.37)
  - Cleveland/Detroit Trip, 1966 Nov (Folder 34.38)
  - California Trip, 1967 Feb (Folder 34.39)
  - Northern New York Vassar Club and AAUW — Schenectady, 1967 Apr (Folder 34.40)
  - Worcester County Vassar Club, 1967 May (Folder 34.41)
  - Milwaukee Vassar Club Trip, 1968 Oct (Folder 34.42)
  - Wildfire Management Institute Meeting, 1969 Mar (Folder 34.43)
  - Texas Trip — Dallas, San Antonio, Houston and California, 1969 Feb (Folder 34.44)
  - Organization of American Historians — Meeting, 1969 Apr (Folder 34.45)
  - Washington and Baltimore Trip — Postponed, 1969 Apr (Folder 34.46)
  - Letter to Alumnae (Coeducation), 1968-1969 (Folder 34.47)
  - Alumnae — General, 1967-1971 (Folder 34.48)
  - Alumnae — A, 1967-1971 (Folder 34.49)
  - Alumnae — B, 1967-1972 (Folder 34.50)
  - Alumnae — C, 1967-1972 (Folder 35.1)
  - Alumnae — D, 1967-1972 (Folder 35.2)
  - Alumnae — E, 1968-1972 (Folder 35.3)
  - Alumnae — F, 1968-1972 (Folder 35.4)
  - Alumnae — G, 1967-1972 (Folder 35.5)
  - Alumnae — H, 1967-1972 (Folder 35.6)
  - Alumnae — I, 1970 (Folder 35.7)
  - Alumnae — J, 1969-1972 (Folder 35.8)
  - Alumnae — K, 1969-1972 (Folder 35.9)
  - Alumnae — L, 1967-1972 (Folder 35.10)
  - Alumnae — Mc, 1969-1971 (Folder 35.11)
  - Alumnae — M, 1967-1972 (Folder 35.12)
  - Alumnae — N, 1968-1972 (Folder 35.13)
  - Alumnae — O, 1967-1972 (Folder 35.14)
  - Alumnae — P, 1967-1972 (Folder 35.15)
  - Alumnae — Q, 1969-1970 (Folder 35.16)
  - Alumnae — R, 1967-1972 (Folder 35.17)
  - Alumnae — S, 1967-1972 (Folder 35.18)
  - Alumnae — T, 1967-1972 (Folder 35.19)
  - Alumnae — V, 1968-1972 (Folder 35.20)
  - Alumnae — W, 1967-1972 (Folder 35.21)
  - Alumnae — X-Y-Z, 1967-1970 (Folder 35.22)
  - AAVC Class Notes, Fall 1971 (Folder 35.23)
  - Associate Alumnae, 1967-1968 (Folder 35.24)
  - Associate Alumnae, 1968-1969 (Folder 35.25)
  - Associate Alumnae, 1969-1970 (Folder 35.26)
  - Associate Alumnae, 1970-1971 (Folder 35.27)
  - Associate Alumnae, 1971-1972 (Folder 35.28)
  - AAVC Centennial Week, 1971 Oct (Folder 35.29)
  - Alumnae Magazine, 1967-1972 (Folder 35.30)
  - Alumnae Reunions, 1967-1969 (Folder 35.31)
  - Reunions, 1970 (Folder 35.32)
  - Reunions, 1971 (Folder 35.33)
  - Reunions, 1972 (Folder 36.1)
  - Classroom Program and Seminar, 1967-1971 (Folder 36.2)
  - Boston Vassar Club, 1967-1970 (Folder 36.3)
  - Buffalo Vassar Club, 1968 Feb (Folder 36.4)
  - Cincinnati Vassar Club, 1969 (Folder 36.5)
  - Dallas-Fort Worth Vassar Club, 1969 (Folder 36.6)
  - New Jersey Vassar Clubs, 1968 (Folder 36.7)
  - New York Vassar Club, 1968-1972 (Folder 36.8)
  - Philadelphia Vassar Club, 1967-1971 (Folder 36.9)
  - Pittsburgh Vassar Club, 1968 (Folder 36.10)
  - Poughkeepsie Vassar Club, 1970 (Folder 36.11)
  - Washington Vassar Club, 1971-1972 (Folder 36.12)
  - Westchester Vassar Club, 1971 (Folder 36.13)
  - Associate Alumnae, 1972-1973 (Folder 36.14)
  - Associate Alumnae (Including New Club Officers), 1973-1974 (Folder 36.15)
  - Associate Alumnae, 1974-1975 (Folder 36.16)
  - Associate Alumnae, 1975-1976 (Folder 36.17)
  - AAVC/Trustee Coordinating Council, 1976 Apr 1 (Folder 36.18)
  - Vassar Quarterly, 1973-1976 (Folder 36.19)
  - Prospective Student Chairmen Visit, 1975 Sep (Folder 36.20)
  - AAVC Class Letters after Reunions, 1976 (Folder 36.21)
  - AAVC Letters from Alumnae after Council meeting, 1972 Oct (Folder 36.22)
  - Alumnae Reunions, 1973-1974 (Folder 36.23)
  - Alumnae Reunion, 1975 (Folder 36.24)
  - AAVC Regional Meeting — Los Angeles, 1974 Nov (Folder 36.25)
  - Class of 1912 Project, 1973 (Folder 36.26)
  - Alumnae — A, 1972-1976 (Folder 36.27)
  - Alumnae — B, 1969-1973 (Folder 36.28)
  - Alumnae — B, 1975-1976 (Folder 36.29)
  - Alumnae — B, 1974-1976 (Folder 36.30)
  - Alumnae — C, 1970-1974 (Folder 36.31)
  - Alumnae — C, 1974-1979 (Folder 36.32)
  - Mrs. Andrew G. Carey, 1949-1979 (Folder 37.1)
  - Alumnae — D, 1972-1976 (Folder 37.2)
  - Alumnae — E, 1972-1976 (Folder 37.3)
  - Alumnae — F, 1971-1976 (Folder 37.4)
  - Alumnae — G, 1970-1976 (Folder 37.5)
  - Alumnae — H, 1969-1976 (Folder 37.6)
  - Alumnae — I, 1972-1974 (Folder 37.7)
  - Alumnae — J, 1968-1976 (Folder 37.8)
  - Alumnae — K, 1972-1976 (Folder 37.9)
  - Alumnae — L, 1972-1976 (Folder 37.10)
  - Alumnae — M, 1971-1974 (Folder 37.11)
  - Alumnae — M, 1974-1976 (Folder 37.12)
  - Alumnae — N, 1972-1976 (Folder 37.13)
  - Alumnae — O, 1972-1976 (Folder 37.14)
  - Alumnae — P, 1972-1976 (Folder 37.15)
  - Alumnae — Q, 1975 (Folder 37.16)
  - Alumnae — R, 1972-1976 (Folder 37.17)
  - Alumnae — S, 1972-1974 (Folder 37.18)
  - Alumnae — S, 1974-1976 (Folder 37.19)
  - Alumnae — T, 1972-1976 (Folder 37.20)
  - Alumnae — U, 1973 (Folder 37.21)
  - Alumnae — V, 1970-1976 (Folder 37.22)
  - Alumnae — W, 1972-1977 (Folder 37.23)
  - Alumnae — X-Y-Z, 1970-1976 (Folder 37.24)
- Series V. Within the College, 1951-1979
  - Annual Reports — Art Department, 1964-1966 (Folder 38.1)
  - Annual Reports — Art Department, 1966-1969 (Folder 38.2)
  - Annual Reports — Art Department, 1973-1977 (Folder 38.3)
  - Annual Report — English Department, 1964-1965 (Folder 38.4)
  - Annual Reports, 1964-1965 (Folder 38.5)
  - Annual Reports — Administration, 1964-1965 (Folder 38.6)
  - Annual Reports (Academic Departments), 1965-1966 (Folder 38.7)
  - Annual Reports (Educational Administration), 1965-1966 (Folder 38.8)
  - Annual Reports — Academic Departments, 1966-1967 (Folder 38.9)
  - Annual Reports — Administrative Offices, 1966-1967 (Folder 38.10)
  - Annual Reports — Academic Departments, 1967-1968 (Folder 38.11)
  - Annual Reports (Administration), 1967-1968 (Folder 38.12)
  - Annual Reports — Academic, 1968-1969 (Folder 39.1)
  - Annual Reports — Administrative, 1968-1969 (Folder 39.2)
  - Annual Report — Dean of Freshmen/Dean of Studies, 1969-1970 (Folder 39.3)
  - Annual Report — Acting Dean of Faculty, 1969-1970 (Folder 39.4)
  - Annual Reports — Departmental, 1969-1970 (Folder 39.5)
  - Annual Report — Administrative, 1969-1970 (Folder 39.6)
  - Annual Reports — Departmental, 1970-1971 (Folder 39.7)
  - Annual Reports — Administrative Officers, 1970-1971 (Folder 39.8)
  - Annual Report — Dean of Faculty, 1970-1971 (Folder 39.9)
  - Annual Reports — Academic Departments, 1971-1972 (Folder 39.10)
  - Annual Report — Dean of Faculty, 1971-1972 (Folder 39.11)
  - Annual Reports — Administrative Officers, 1971-1972 (Folder 39.12)
  - Annual Reports — Academic Departments, 1972-1973 (Folder 39.13)
  - Annual Reports — Administration, 1972-1973 (Folder 39.14)
  - Annual Report — Dean of the Faculty, 1972-1973 (Folder 40.1)
  - Annual Reports — Academic, 1973-1974 (Folder 40.2)
  - Annual Report — Dean of the Faculty, 1973-1974 (Folder 40.3)
  - Annual Reports — Administration, 1973-1974 (Folder 40.4)
  - Annual Reports — Academic, 1974-1975 (Folder 40.5)
  - Annual Reports — Administration, 1974-1975 (Folder 40.6)
  - Annual Report — Dean of Faculty, 1974-1975 (Folder 40.7)
  - Annual Reports — Academic (Folder 1), 1975-1976 (Folder 40.8)
  - Annual Reports — Academic (Folder 2), 1975-1976 (Folder 40.9)
  - Annual Report — Dean of Faculty, 1975-1976 (Folder 40.10)
  - Annual Reports — Administration, 1975-1976 (Folder 40.11)
  - Annual Reports — Academic, 1976-1977 (Folder 41.1)
  - Annual Reports — Programs and Committees, 1976-1977 (Folder 41.2)
  - Annual Reports — Administration, 1976-1977 (Folder 41.3)
  - Annual Report — Acting Dean of Faculty, 1976-1977 (Folder 41.4)
  - Gifts — General and Anonymous, 1964-1966 (Folder 41.5)
  - Gifts — A, 1964-1966 (Folder 41.6)
  - Gifts — B, 1964-1966 (Folder 41.7)
  - Gifts — C, 1964-1966 (Folder 41.8)
  - Gifts — D, 1964-1966 (Folder 41.9)
  - Gifts — E, 1964-1966 (Folder 41.10)
  - Gifts — F, 1964-1966 (Folder 41.11)
  - Gifts — G, 1964-1966 (Folder 41.12)
  - Gifts — H, 1964-1966 (Folder 41.13)
  - Gifts — I, 1964-1966 (Folder 41.14)
  - Gifts — J, 1964-1966 (Folder 41.15)
  - Gifts — K, 1964-1966 (Folder 41.16)
  - Gifts — L, 1964-1966 (Folder 41.17)
  - Gifts — M, 1964-1966 (Folder 41.18)
  - Gifts — N, 1964-1966 (Folder 41.19)
  - Gifts — O, 1964-1966 (Folder 41.20)
  - Gifts — P, 1964-1966 (Folder 41.21)
  - Gifts — Q, 1964-1966 (Folder 41.22)
  - Gifts — R, 1964-1966 (Folder 41.23)
  - Gifts — S, 1964-1966 (Folder 41.24)
  - Gifts — T, 1964-1966 (Folder 41.25)
  - Gifts — U, 1965-1966 (Folder 41.26)
  - Gifts — V, 1964-1966 (Folder 41.27)
  - Gifts — W, 1964-1966 (Folder 41.28)
  - Gifts — X-Y-Z, 1964-1966 (Folder 41.29)
  - Gifts — Miscellaneous and Anonymous, 1966-1967 (Folder 42.1)
  - Gifts — Miscellaneous and Anonymous, 1967-1969 (Folder 42.2)
  - Gifts — A, 1966-1967 (Folder 42.3)
  - Gifts — A, 1967-1969 (Folder 42.4)
  - Gifts — B, 1966-1967 (Folder 42.5)
  - Gifts — B, 1967-1969 (Folder 42.6)
  - Gifts — C, 1966-1967 (Folder 42.7)
  - Gifts — C, 1967-1969 (Folder 42.8)
  - Gifts — D, 1966-1967 (Folder 42.9)
  - Gifts — D, 1967-1969 (Folder 42.10)
  - Gifts — E, 1966-1967 (Folder 42.11)
  - Gifts — E, 1967-1969 (Folder 42.12)
  - Gifts — F, 1966-1967 (Folder 42.13)
  - Gifts — F, 1967-1969 (Folder 42.14)
  - Gifts — G, 1966-1967 (Folder 42.15)
  - Gifts — G, 1967-1969 (Folder 42.16)
  - Gifts — H, 1966-1967 (Folder 42.17)
  - Gifts — H, 1967-1969 (Folder 42.18)
  - Gifts — I, 1966-1967 (Folder 42.19)
  - Gifts — I, 1967-1969 (Folder 42.20)
  - Gifts — J, 1966-1967 (Folder 42.21)
  - Gifts — J, 1967-1969 (Folder 42.22)
  - Gifts — K, 1966-1967 (Folder 42.23)
  - Gifts — K, 1967-1969 (Folder 42.24)
  - Gifts — L, 1966-1967 (Folder 42.25)
  - Gifts — L, 1967-1969 (Folder 42.26)
  - Gifts — M, 1966-1967 (Folder 42.27)
  - Gifts — M, 1967-1969 (Folder 42.28)
  - Gifts — N, 1966-1967 (Folder 42.29)
  - Gifts — N, 1967-1969 (Folder 42.30)
  - Gifts — O, 1966-1967 (Folder 42.31)
  - Gifts — O, 1967-1969 (Folder 42.32)
  - Gifts — P, 1966-1967 (Folder 42.33)
  - Gifts — P, 1967-1969 (Folder 42.34)
  - Gifts — Q, 1966-1967 (Folder 42.35)
  - Gifts — Q, 1968 (Folder 42.36)
  - Gifts — R, 1966-1967 (Folder 42.37)
  - Gifts — R, 1967-1969 (Folder 42.38)
  - Gifts — S, 1966-1967 (Folder 42.39)
  - Gifts — S, 1967-1969 (Folder 42.40)
  - Gifts — T, 1966-1967 (Folder 42.41)
  - Gifts — T, 1967-1969 (Folder 42.42)
  - Gifts — U, 1966-1967 (Folder 42.43)
  - Gifts — U, 1967-1969 (Folder 42.44)
  - Gifts — V, 1966-1967 (Folder 42.45)
  - Gifts — V, 1967-1969 (Folder 42.46)
  - Gifts — W, 1966-1967 (Folder 42.47)
  - Gifts — W, 1967-1969 (Folder 42.48)
  - Gifts — X-Y-Z, 1966-1967 (Folder 42.49)
  - Gifts — X-Y-Z, 1967-1969 (Folder 42.50)
  - Sloan Foundation — Proposal for Science Grant, 1966 (Folder 43.1)
  - Potential Donors, 1964-1966 (Folder 43.2)
  - Bequests, 1962-1967 (Folder 43.3)
  - Bequests, 1967-1972 (Folder 43.4)
  - Annuities, 1964-1966 (Folder 43.5)
  - Annuities, 1967-1972 (Folder 43.6)
  - Life Income Contracts — A-J, 1964-1967 (Folder 43.7)
  - Life Income Contracts — K-Z, 1964-1967 (Folder 43.8)
  - Life Income Contracts — A-J, 1967-1972 (Folder 43.9)
  - Life Income Contracts — K-Z, 1967-1972 (Folder 43.10)
  - Annuities, 1972-1974 (Folder 43.11)
  - Bequests, 1972-1974 (Folder 43.12)
  - Life Income Contracts — A-J, 1972-1974 (Folder 43.13)
  - Life Income Contracts — K-Z, 1972-1974 (Folder 43.14)
  - Miscellaneous and Anonymous, 1969-1972 (Folder 43.15)
  - Gifts — A, 1969-1972 (Folder 43.16)
  - Gifts — A, 1972-1974 (Folder 43.17)
  - Gifts — B, 1969-1972 (Folder 43.18)
  - Gifts — B, 1972-1974 (Folder 43.19)
  - Gifts — C, 1969-1972 (Folder 43.20)
  - Gifts — C, 1972-1974 (Folder 43.21)
  - Gifts — D, 1969-1972 (Folder 43.22)
  - Gifts — D, 1972-1974 (Folder 43.23)
  - Gifts — E, 1969-1972 (Folder 43.24)
  - Gifts — E, 1972-1974 (Folder 43.25)
  - Gifts — F, 1969-1972 (Folder 43.26)
  - Gifts — F, 1972-1974 (Folder 43.27)
  - Gifts — G, 1969-1972 (Folder 44.1)
  - Gifts — G, 1972-1974 (Folder 44.2)
  - Gifts — H, 1969-1972 (Folder 44.3)
  - Gifts — H, 1972-1974 (Folder 44.4)
  - Gifts — I, 1969-1972 (Folder 44.5)
  - Gifts — I, 1972-1974 (Folder 44.6)
  - Gifts — J, 1969-1972 (Folder 44.7)
  - Gifts — J, 1972-1974 (Folder 44.8)
  - Gifts — K, 1969-1972 (Folder 44.9)
  - Gifts — K, 1972-1974 (Folder 44.10)
  - Gifts — L, 1969-1972 (Folder 44.11)
  - Gifts — L, 1972-1974 (Folder 44.12)
  - Gifts — M, 1969-1972 (Folder 44.13)
  - Gifts — M, 1972-1974 (Folder 44.14)
  - Gifts — N, 1969-1972 (Folder 44.15)
  - Gifts — N, 1972-1974 (Folder 44.16)
  - Gifts — O, 1969-1972 (Folder 44.17)
  - Gifts — O, 1972-1974 (Folder 44.18)
  - Gifts — P, 1969-1972 (Folder 44.19)
  - Gifts — P, 1972-1974 (Folder 44.20)
  - Gifts — Q, 1969-1971 (Folder 44.21)